special
[Music]
live I don't know about you
guys but I like living on the edge well
I don't know if but I guess so I have no
choice I believe and today is living on
the edge and I'll tell you why in just a
moment so good afternoon and welcome to
a very special uh Edition 2m Edition
live Edition uh we don't usually go live
at this hour but we did because we have
such a special guest of the Don Lemon
show so um so much news today I felt
that streams at 10 am and 5:00 pm that
just wasn't enough and so we're going to
dig into tons of topics this hour and
I'm so blessed to have a co-pilot by my
side someone who knows all about the
issues especially what's going on in the
world today and that is none other than
drum roll Amanda
seals do you want a drum roll because I
have one on hand yeah do it is an
artistic intellectual
[Music]
Amanda Steels an artistic intellectual
and the host of the YouTube show views
from Amanda land how you
[Applause]
doing I love it I love it I love it it's
good to see you Tom it's good to see you
how are you I've been trying to get you
forever forever in that like one um eyes
Don I'm a very reachable person we have
a lot of mutuals we do have a lot of
mutuals but I know especially ever since
you got woke now I'm like all right son
call me up I used to tear you up know
know I always been woke I've always been
woke well now that you've been loudly
woke I've been working in corporate
media now that I'm out was working in
corporate media I feel free it's amazing
but as you tie on I love it but here
look let me no as you know it's It Ain't
Easy out here in these here streets for
us for people who just really speak
their mind and say um you know our uh
wow we're going there quick our I
believe our um skin tone makes us not
brand safe and automatically political
and
controversial um and you know I don't
know and sometimes our the our
counterparts in the larger culture they
don't get that sort of stigma attached
to them whether you think it's a stigma
or not so that's why can I translate
what you said yeah black folks don't get
to talk so freely as the whites that's
what you just said yeah that's what I
just said but um I think that there is
often times by white folks an
expectation that light-skinned black
folks are going to talk more safely and
then when we show up and defy Massa from
the inside out they're like ah we didn't
expect
this you're crazy no I'm just brilliant
that's different no I think you're you
are but look I'm glad that you're here
and we had one little thing that I
thought was a little weird because I
think you had an incident with a Booker
that was a little odd who did not know I
think someone was trying to book you for
the show and you're like wait a minute
do I know who this person is and
whatever because because there's
scammers that like you're the only real
person in out of like 13 scammers that
have tried to book me in like the last
six months and they SC yeah and they
scam You by saying we're g to pay you
this money to come on our podcast or to
come on this show and it'll be Joe Rogan
it'll be Glennon Doyle like they'll just
pick anybody and then the whole scam is
that you send them your payment
information information and they're like
ha gotcha oh no no no no so I was like
is you real are you the real Don Lemon
or are you fwn tomato like what is this
are you do you ever would you consider
going on those shows would you go on a
Rogan or a conservative podcast do you
do
that um I don't know I really try to
keep myself in very peaceful places
these days you know I know I us I don't
know how valuable that would be that's
what I I'm glad you said that because I
have a dilemma they invite me to go on
these conservative things all the time
and I used to like take them up on it
and sometimes maybe I'll go back but I
feel like lately I've had to protect my
peace and I also don't want to go
somewhere where they're going to attack
attack me personally you know what I'm
saying yes I went on Club Shay I had no
idea I was going to be attacked
personally by like a a a brother but I I
completely understand that because I
make it my business to be like okay
what's going on over here let me look in
how how's their comment section like how
do they operate Etc but I think
sometimes they bring Someone Like You on
because they're like he's a respectable
black so we can like they don't expect
you to turn up they don't expect you to
I don't know like basically get at them
so they think it's going to be what they
consider to be like a real respectable
conversation um I don't know they hate
me they you know they they don't like
recently but that's just recently
because recently you've gotten really
good at doing what I call the Columbia
curse out because I went to Columbia for
grad school and ever so often people
forget that and then when I decide to
curse them out as a as a you know
bibliophile with a great vocabulary
they're like and that feels even more
offensive than cursing them out with the
curse words because they they don't even
know what you're saying they don't even
know the words but they're actually
shocked when you talk about light-skin I
I feel like you know because I was in
corporate media so that's kind of a
that's light-skin being in corporate
media just you know what I mean in a
weird way but when I say words like if I
say [ __ ] or [ __ ] or whatever they're
like oh my God Don said oh my God and
like if I call someone is way Brady
gonna have to it
same thing yes why did wait can I ask
you something why did you feel attacked
on Club Shay because I was being
attacked because I every experience I
shared was being undermined and uh
questioned with doubt of
legitimacy H interesting okay all right
across the board my autism my RAC like
experience with racism they even cut out
when he says straight up it seems like
anybody who doesn't agree with you you
just say they racist they cut that out
and I was like that's real for real
yeah oh wow wow he said that's straight
up they cut it they cut it Don and I
said and I said and they cut this and I
was like I feel like you're coming at me
with a lot of hostility and he was like
no I'm not and he got a you know he got
a his shoulders got a little movement in
them and they you know he kind he he
didn't keep on with that but I at a
certain point in that interview just
decided like oh I'm going to have to
deploy what many women have become very
skilled at which is
using Gifts of uh
diffusion are are you guys friendly now
are you okay no you're
not I'm sorry is there anything I can do
I don't really know on that there's
nothing I can do no no it was just it
was it was deep unkindness and he stood
on it so there's no reason to even go
further in that well let me just say
this um if I'm unkind in any way let me
know just tell me straight up I have no
intention of being unkind or whatever no
seriously because I like to I like to
have respectful conversations I don't I
don't like to insult people but
sometimes you do ask probing questions
and sometimes people do get offended by
it and if you are just let me know you
know what I'm saying yeah absolutely uh
can you see the comments are up people
are are loving you so do you see no some
people in here are just mean and I'd be
like what what type of people are they
someone say you need to take your meds
you're right I I I tried to take my Lexa
Pro today and it accidentally went down
the drain and it was too expensive so I
was like I'm not gonna bother with it it
could be in that little you know dip in
the bottom that you may be able to get
to but I don't know if you're handy that
way so do you believe I'm so glad you
said that um we're going this is stream
of Consciousness I have this whole thing
planned but I love taking the stigma off
of mental health and I think if you need
a little if you need some help I talk
about how I you know well I had been on
I did like Pro not is it PR Prozac a
long time ago and then um that was like
the first I would say like marketed one
wouldn't you say this was in that yeah
2000 early 2000s and then when I had an
incident when I was racially profiled
and I sort of went into a depression
like because it was public where I where
I lived and then um you know when I left
CNN but that was more for me it was more
preventative because I knew I think that
I've always had um like a low-grade
depression my entire life and so I you
know when I left CNN I was like well I
um you know you I wasn't I wasn't like I
was down a little bit and I didn't want
to get yeah I didn't want to get to the
bad place yeah and I kept resisting it
saying I'm not it's not like that
because there was a kind of a weird
sense of relief after I left right like
I'm like oh okay I don't have to deal
with that anymore but then it was like
because it played out so publicly and a
lot of it was lies and stuff you know
that kind of gets to you crazy right and
so I said you know I need to do this and
then you know so the um bpion or
whatever um it's working out that's it's
called it's well beat is basically what
it is yeah does it help yeah it helps I
think it does help and I I think it's
okay I think that people should have
therapy we shouldn't be as black folks
trying to say pray the the pray and and
go see your pastor or whatever like they
used to tell me pray the gay away that
doesn't work so you know oh no it wasn't
Prozac sorry I'm wrong someone in the
chat reminded me it was zolof is what I
took and it actually worked well yeah
yeah yeah so any I mean I think um also
we're living in times that are a bit
more heavy and extreme in the United
States than we were before so I know for
me I feel like what I may have been able
to manage previously with what I know
now and what and the weight of things
that are happening now like I just
didn't feel like I could continue to
manage in the same way yeah so then what
what is your advice and how do you help
others at least with the stigma I I
always try to help others if I'm dealing
with something I'm like how can I help
you know so how do you how does do you
think talking about it you just being so
absolutely about it helpful I think
ultimately stigma is really attached to
shame and you know when we see RFK Jr
coming after these meds and really
enacting Eugenics and the idea that it
is abnormal to have you know neurod
Divergence it's abnormal to have uh
disability Etc it is incredibly normal
for human beings to have different ways
of existing that is completely normal
and uh what is abnormal is the
commitment to not being willing to just
talk about that and create space for
that so that's what I try to do all
right so so y' if you you know um you
can one of the great resources is uh
Psychology today for finding um Mental
Health Providers and I know some I know
insurance is incredibly difficult as
well uh but a lot of uh universities
that have psych programs you can
actually go and at least get counseling
even if you can't get prescriptions you
can get counseling from students in
those programs who are getting their
hours and that can be really helpful
would you ever do um like drug therapy
you know with like um you know AOC cybin
or something that I'm afraid of you
would you're afraid of that yeah is
my brain is like this sweater you know
it's a
lot you know it's it's it's a lot going
on in there I'm afraid I mean like I
feel like I can suit myself up and
eventually do iasa but it needs to be
like a whole experience I need to be in
Brazil with the shaman like it has to be
a whole
thing yeah well I when I when I had the
CNN Plus show I had a talk show and I
talked I did this thing about drug
therapy guided therapy and it really
helped like members of the military and
people had PTSD and people who were
suicidal and so I became very open and I
tried and you know actually it was you
know just a little bit I dabbled and um
hey look if it works for you did it work
for you at all I think it worked a
little bit I think sometimes like as you
know I I'm a big proponent of therapy
talk therapy but I think talk therapy
can only go so far and I think very
rarely do people have you know
epiphanies or breakthroughs they do
happen but it's after a lot a lot of
talk and think years of therapy usually
you know everybody's experience is
different and so I think that sometimes
with those things when you think about
look you think
about um I can't mention you know the
letter the L the whatever and the D
right um I'm I'm trying not to have the
the AI pick up and then you
know so
um Those Were Meant to ex as mind
expansion oh Luc in the sky yeah yeah
those are meant to expand you and so
that's what they were originally meant
for not to not recreational and I think
that you know if it works you it works
for you with diamonds um remember the
brother who was like I'm micro do and
heroin I was like bro I guess dang I
just messed up the whole you can't say
that yeah you can say that dang you
literally just said that I'm sorry guys
I know hope don't hopefully uh Tik Tok I
hope you're not listening okay so listen
let's get into this you are an artistic
intellectual what does that mean
Amanda so I came up with this because uh
of two main things one I've had a lot of
different titles because I've been multi
a multi-hyphenate and I've been like
legitimately in number of spaces so I
was like a legitimate DJ at a certain
point I've been in a legit I've been a
legitimate host uh I've been an actress
a comedian and at this phase in my life
it felt like none of those titles really
represented what my purpose and
intention is at this phase after leaving
La leaving Hollywood divesting from this
concept of celebrity and the and the
actual effort at trying to be you know
in studios and production deals and blah
blah blah blah blah um and and I thought
about like well where am I right now and
really all I care about right now is
using my art to educate like that's all
I care about is using my art to educate
and make edutainment in addition to that
we are in the midst of the age of idiocy
H this is a time where it's imperative
for fascists to actually uh suppress
intellectualism they need you to be dumb
they need you to be disinterested they
need you to be unable to have discourse
uh without ostracizing each other like
that's a that they need that they need
you to hate everyone who's different be
able to find common ground and you need
critical thinking to do that you need
comparative analysis skills you need uh
not just being smart but you need
intelligence you anybody could be smart
intelligence is the synthesis of those
ideas of those of that information into
new ideas that move us forward so that
is where I exist and that is where I and
I had fallen off I fell off from that
because I was so immersed in the goal of
you know what it takes to succeed in
Hollywood and um it feels really good to
be back in a place of being led with
learning and so the artistic
intellectual is my title and it's not to
say that there haven't been artistic
intellectuals who have come before us
there's so many Nina Simone James
Baldwin Gil Scott Haren but they didn't
have this title and and we live in a
place you noce people need titles they
need labels Etc so for those who may be
trying to figure out what that
trajectory is for them and there isn't
something that is laid out but they they
feel what I feel this can be a guide for
them we are talking to Amanda seals
today an artistic intellectual the host
of the YouTube show views from Amanda
land make sure you tune in make sure you
hit the thumbs up make sure you like us
make sure you subscribe that's how we
stay on these digital streets these
Independent Media streets is from your
generous support and it doesn't cost you
anything to hit the thumbs up or to
subscribe it is free uh and if you want
to become a member it's at the top of
our chat so um thank you Amanda seals
for being on today so Amanda when
you um you talk about divesting from all
of these things and you you spoke about
intellectual is different from smart and
I try to get people to understand that I
think we also throw around this word
genius a little too much these days this
person's a genius that person's a genius
I'm like Albert Einstein was a genius
okay um but I'm not do you how do you
define genius I think it's it's someone
it's people who um I just got a
restriction on the thing really yes I
don't know why is that on Tik Tok yeah
oh well I'm just saying it's annoying
yeah because it's often time it's hard
sometimes to just tell the news on here
because the news is counter to their
Community
rules what do you mean by that yes what
well because everything is so terrible
and they're like don't talk about
controversy don't talk about this that
and the third and you're like but this
this that and the third is what is
taking
place yeah they yoking Folks up yeah
okay so um the so when you talk about
the difference between smart you said
how do I Define a genius I Define a
genius as as someone who who who um
invents something creates something
comes up with a theory of relativity um
you know comes up with a you know
formulas and and and and does things
that no other people like you you need a
mind and intellect and like you said
intelligence to be able to do it now I
think that there is a certain genius or
uh a talent in someone who sees an idea
and takes it to the next level right uh
or sees like a great Creator and then
they go oh I like that or I'm gonna buy
this company I'm gonna change it that is
a talent within itself this is but to me
it's not about unless you're sort of
creating something or doing or you know
you your mind takes you to a place that
is different than what other people are
thinking or whatever that's genius to me
but I'm going on defying the grid right
okay but when when you talk about
intelligence versus uh smart you said
you need intelligence a lot of people
say oh I love such and such they're so
smart like you know Candace Owens or
something I said they're so intelligent
I say no they're may be smart but
sometimes people just talk fast and you
think they're smart you know what I'm
saying or they're just saying things
that you don't know about right just a
fast talker right right right
right the faster that
certain people are talking the more you
know like if you can't get the point
across first of all I'm always like the
truth is a short route it don't really
be taking the whole essay
y'all if you're explaining you're losing
like licky split as a comic that's what
I that was really what turned the corner
from me trying to be a comic to me like
officially understanding how I need how
I could exist as a comic it was like
stop trying to convince the audience say
the joke say the joke and keep it moving
and that's um but sorry I'm I'm going
off track but
you're this concept of smart at this
point is applied in spaces that I feel
like
are ignoring things like um access you
know like someone might say like Elon
Musk is smart and it's like well I think
he's savvy I also want to point out I
feel like let me know what you think
about this I feel like there's a
difference between being smart and being
Savvy and what I say is the difference
is that
um smart is being able to synthesize and
process information fairly quickly uh
and remember it and and regurgitate it
and put it Forward um but also being
able to and when I say process
information it can also be like your dog
is smart because it was able to say like
oh that's doing that and that's doing
that so I'm going to have to do this
route where whereas another dog might be
like I don't even know what's going on
here
savy Savvy is I know how to work within
the capitalist system and make money and
the reason I say that is because Don I
met a lot of people that are good at
making money that ain't
smart they ain't smart but they're
really Adept at the white man's
system of
Economics what you
mean because that's what capitalism is
capitalism is not just Commerce it's not
just you know Merchant trading
capitalism is
exploitation go
on in order for capitalism to exist it
requires exploitation cuz it cuz profit
margin requires something somebody
either getting less than they should or
somebody paying more than they should
right so if I make this pencil for
$2 um ultimately the most I should
realistically be selling this for is
like $4 right but in capitalism it's
like nah I'mma charge
$25 oh I was going to say 10 but you
went there but people will do I mean
Donald Trump was charging like a hundred
something dollars for a Bible like you
didn't write
this um and so if you to me if you can't
justify the reason so for instance like
these are my Harriet Tubman pistol pins
right so these pins are $20 and that
adds up because that's the cost of the
pin How It's Made that's the shipping of
the pin right but that's also um the
design that I drew so it is my original
artwork that you're getting a piece of
and it's also attached to my name and my
name has its own value so that's how I
create the value system around its price
of $20 and in capitalism there is no
ceiling for that which is where we are
there's also not a free market
so you know you have monopolies and all
of these things and so when we talk
about capitalism I think it becomes a
buzzword but on a basic ground level it
really just means
exploitation H wow can we can we excuse
me talk about anything even um we can
talk about topics right did you know
about the congestion pricing What's
Happening Here in Manhattan and mayor
Eric Adams and all that stuff and did
you know about that I heard about it
okay it is a piece of work and by by
that I mean a terrible person well I
only because I just got this from
producers and I want to know what you
think so put this up here's so that
people were upset about congestion
pricing that this
is uh I you know Donald Trump just
posted congestion pricing is dead
Manhattan and all of New York is saved
long live the king so I guess he's
calling himself the king here and then
Trump calls himself the king Aaron rupar
is putting up here this is about
capitalism about making money also about
you know whatever and you know what Eric
Adams just did he went down he kissed
the ring and then Donald Trump asked the
New York City the folks the justice
department asked the New York the New
York folks to drop the charges against
Eric Adams so what say you about all of
this Donald Trump is a king and Eric
Adams new relationship new Love Fest
with Donald Trump
well I mean we all know that that Donald
Trump's relationship with Eric Adams is
just so Eric Adams can have his charges
dropped but what we aren't seeing a lot
of is the protests that are happening in
New York saying Kathy holel who does
have the power as the governor to remove
Eric Adams should exercise that power
when Eric Adams is actively saying which
is going against what he originally said
he originally was like you know we
cannot support the Ice uh efforts at
deportation we are a sanctuary Sanctuary
City and he's literally like n I'm good
we can do that he's on couches on
Fox talking about yeah I got it with
this Zar telling
him if you don't I'mma come get you I'm
like he said I'm gonna be all up your
butt that's what he did say that he said
I'm gonna be up your butt and I was like
okay and he laughed ha haa and that
those are the times when I want someone
to said my bad y'all I was on drugs
because I want to believe that you were
impaired when you allowed that to happen
on National Television but that's what
you know we're continuously seeing the
the effort of Donald Trump to exercise
and expand his power not just in like
these grandiose statements but with the
effort of um saying that only the
executive office can determine what his
law and when he does things like this
outside of the federal office right
outside of the Office of the President
but in basically saying look New York I
did this for you um he is trying to I
guess you know just use his tentacles to
get his feet deeper rooted in the people
as a problem solver which we know for a
fact that he is not right the same way
that he didn't solve the scenarios with
Canada and Mexico yeah well and that was
all that was all just a show right
because he hisone and he could have done
the very same thing but it's part of a
show every day already been done yeah he
already been done yeah well I mean far
as far as he him negotiating right but
had already been negotiated yeah they
had already agreed to this they was like
no no I know what you're saying that was
agree to but if he wanted to go further
in negotiations rather than doing it
publicly he could have picked up the
phone and he could have called Trudeau
right and just said hey let's talk more
about and try to make another you know
try to expand upon this deal instead he
made he makes everything a show and I
believe the things that they make a show
show I believe it's a distraction from
the real [ __ ] that they're doing behind
the scenes you know hiding their hands
and then they're just telling you like
look at this oh we're gonna change it
Gulf of America one million percent yeah
so and then all slight of hand it's all
slight of hand so what do you think the
king I think he actually thinks he's the
king I really do well I mean on paper he
is yeah right now is he that's a good
question is he the King right now he has
all three according to the Supreme Court
saying that is impervious
to you know punishment he can't quote
unquote break the law so he is uh for
all intents and purposes
Sovereign how do you feel about
that um how do I feel about that I'm not
surprised I
feel I feel that that has somewhat been
unspoken and it's just now on paper um I
feel that a lot of what we are seeing
right now something that frustrates me
is people talking about where we are now
in a silo as if there
weren't um there wasn't an environment
created for this and this has been like
a systemic growth into this place that
we're in right so it wasn't like this
was um like coups don't happen without
you know what it's like Don it's like
when people say you can't break up a
happy home mhm
mhm America wasn't
happy well America was great and they're
just trying to take it back to when
America was great I was like where is he
going with
this I was so concerned for those 2.2
seconds so you know I I talked about
this on the show yesterday on what on
views from Amanda views from amandel
land that
um when they say that when they say make
America great again a lot of people will
be like what does that mean mean what
does that mean and you know when was
America ever great for white men America
was great at its Inception pre- Civil
War it was great they were the only ones
who had power landowning white men were
the only ones had power to make laws
they were the only ones who had power to
amass wealth and that was great uh for
them and then over time we have seen
that expand and every time it expands
they see it as they see the expansion so
you know it's like if if they're sitting
at a table instead of them seeing the
table grow they see it as like someone
is scooching into the same size table
when that's not what's happening the the
expansion is happening in the sense that
we are we are lengthening the table to
make more people be able to sit at it
we're putting leaves in the table
another Leaf in the table yes and uh but
there for some reason this making model
of man is incredibly in Secure to the
point where I often times Wonder like
are they human this is so the the
existence the commitment to detriment at
all costs for the retainment of this
power is it seems to me inhumane and now
we see other folks in much larger
numbers Beyond white men you know
flocking to this type of mentality and
that's what's really concerning to me
it's aspirational they they they aspire
to it but they don't understand that
they are still who they are you know
what I'm saying uh Kathy hokel released
a statement just so we um Amanda seals
and I were just talking about this
Donald Trump you see it up on the screen
calling himself a king long live the
king statement from Governor Kathy
hokel excuse me everyone on congesting
congestion pricing public transit life
blood in New York City critical economic
Futures in New Yorker president Trump
knows very well since this uh since this
first in nation program took effect blah
blah blah and then she goes in you know
on what happened okay we are a nation of
laws not ruled by a king the MTA has
initiated legal proceedings in the
southern district of New York to
preserve this critical program we'll see
you in court here's my thing these
people are always putting out these
statements are always saying this and
and and and so we'll get to the
Democrats I don't know any New Yorkers
who like this what you mean the
congestion pricing no I'm not I'm not
I'm not I'm not congestion pricing is
like not if you like it I'm talking
about the process of the king and he got
rid of it
and and you have Kathy hokel saying
we're going to do this in court my
question is I'm going to get to he's a
king what is the point of the courts all
right exactly so then do you think that
she should get rid of Eric
Adams
yes
yes if you claim to be against
Fascism and you want to resist fascism
you need to do everything in your power
to do that and by the way many folks are
going to be forced to do things not in
our power in order to do that so that is
a reality she is one of the unique cases
where she can actively use her power to
protect the people of her state which is
what she was been empowered to do um she
I I doubt she will do it because
Democrats seem I don't know like it
seems like a part of an oath take where
it's like I'm not going to do too I'm
never going to do too much Democrats
don't never do too much did you say o no
I
said an oath they take okay I'm like
wait
what o you took it back talk I was
talking
[Music]
Jive no but I I I you know shout out to
um Alami urin because she really does
not play about
her dissection and disdain of this man
um and there are people that are in line
for instance the next person in line
after him would be Jermaine D Williams
that is the person who would take over
this like there are there's um secession
for when people are removed from office
there is session and JY Williams who is
the public advocate for the City of New
York is who the next person would be and
let me just tell you now y'all jande D
Williams is is beyond Progressive and
he's and he knows the people and he's
with the people and he's also from
grenade L up all spice Island
[Laughter]
massive so look um I I'm wondering know
if he look I I don't know is she going
to get rid of him I think that it was
it's probably in her best interest and
the city's best interest especially when
you have lost the confidence of of every
um Deputy Commissioner around you he's
lost the room and so why and then but so
why keep him but
um if he runs again he might stand a
chance of winning and I'm hearing that
you know Cuomo is going to do it and and
and is the front runner and will win
even with me too and all of that
I think that anything said
today needs to be re-evaluated
tomorrow for at least until further
notice anybody who's making like plans
you know how they say like you playing
and God laughs
well people had jobs yesterday right
they don't got them today they had plans
they said we going to Bermuda no you're
not right right you know people had
plans they were committed to voting for
Trump and then he completely flipped
their whole existence on their head so I
think when we talk about predictions of
who could win and who could not win um
yeah I just think we're in a real time
of on one hand chaos but it has a real
opportunity for birth to take place in
ways that hasn't before from Coalition
building and from community building and
from folks really believing you know uh
there's space for me that may not have
been there
before um okay so you're very outspoken
and I'm I'm gonna ask you a couple
questions so it's he say no stop it um I
saw this isn't a name drop so I won't
even say the person's name but there a
very do the name job do the name it was
Patty Lael so I saw Patty Lael and I
went and talked to her she goes you know
what done I said yes ma'am she said I
think people are scared of you I think
they're afraid of you you and I said why
they said because they're not used to
people like you speaking your mind and I
said well yeah I know and she goes no no
no I mean that really scared so do you
think people are scared of you because
you are more outspoken than I am
yeah absolutely people are scared of me
people are annoyed by me look at your
chat you know people are that does that
bother you of
course not as much as it used to but
it's just it's typically related to
things that are just not true so that's
what bothers me yeah yeah yeah if it you
know when it's related to things that
are actual I'm like okay you know you're
en TI of your opinion but a lot of times
when you really get to it folks are like
saying
nonsense and you're like I had I had one
person say you know why I don't like
Amanda seals because she clearly is
doing has an agenda with her hair
my agenda is that I really don't want to
do my hair no more so I locked my hair
so that it was so that doing my hair was
no longer on my agenda but um but
I I feel like also you know you get to a
certain point in your spiritual
growth where you also
understand that you're not just speaking
for yourself like I know for me I am
speaking through the voice of my Spirit
guides I'm speak like that's what this
Harriet is like that's my ancestor on
the main line speaking to me right um I
know that there's only so serious that I
can take myself because I am a part of a
movement that has to happen right so you
know when people will be like oh
Amanda's full of herself it's like no I
am uh not full of myself in the way that
you think about it I'm full of myself in
the fact that I am not a hollow soul
like I am full of things
that have value and uh principle and
morals and I stand on those every day
and
um that makes people also uncomfortable
because like the same way I've had dudes
that I dated say like I can't be with
you because you're too good yeah like
I'm G to be expected to to do that and
for what it's worth I am a human like
everybody else and I make mistakes yeah
look I understand that the being
unbothered but then being bothered by uh
things that are just not true which is
why I what I told you in the beginning
when you know after when I was the last
part when I was at C and when I left
like there was so many things that
weren't true but I couldn't defend
myself because I was under a contract
right you know what I'm talking about
yeah so you mentioned you mentioned um
growth you said this is an opportunity
So speaking of opportunities let's talk
about the Democrats for which the reason
I asked you if you if people are afraid
of views because you've been very
critical of the Democrats you know they
don't like being criticized um Jasmine
Crockett was on The View and I'm going
to play a little bit of it today uh and
a little bit of it and she was on today
and then you and I going to discuss okay
so let's play it m get this Breakneck
Pace it feels like signing all these EOS
doing these long ranging press
conferences in the Oval Office um
Democrats seem to not be getting their
footing on what the message and strategy
is to push back we think of the leaders
chanting we will win outside of Treasury
which was widely panned you've talked
about Democrats needing a branding
overhaul are you satisfied with the
approach so far and what do they need to
do to trying to get the mojo back I you
know what I think that just like um the
rest of the world we've got a bit of
whiplash because for some people even
those that voted for him they said well
we've been here before and we didn't
fall apart the last time he was here so
we won't fall apart this time and so I
think that while we had the Playbook
right there for us project 2025 I still
think that even some Democrats were like
oh well he's just going to do what he
did last time and he's not world leaders
are recognizing that he's not the same I
mean he's 10 times worse and imagine
that this is the guy that oversaw how
many deaths during covid right and now
we had Ebola breakout now we've got
measles breaks this is bird flu cuz they
were some of the other people that got
fired no and he's like oh well wait a
minute like this is just literally not
even partisanship in my opinion at this
point this is incompetence
what do you think she's on The View um
she's talking I think right now she's
probably the most honest and maybe the
most she's the youngest and sort of
forward facing facing modern version of
a Democrat her and AOC and maybe Maxwell
Frost um so what do you think so far and
then we'll play a little bit
more so I actually texted Jasmine a
couple like maybe last week and just
said uh you know you're the only one
over there with a
spine she may not have hit me back but
she saw the
text
and
um one of the things that's unique about
Jasmine is she's also not a career
politician right so she was a
lawyer um she came into this space as an
adult so like when I got into comedy I
was already like 30 five right so I
wasn't I didn't I had less ability to be
indoctrinated or to really be like U
molded by who was there and I also had a
faster pace of success because I already
knew my voice and I think that's part of
what we're witnessing with Jasmine she's
coming into this position as a grown
woman who has already got her bones
about her and who doesn't need it she
doesn't need this position she could go
back and make way more money if that was
her goal as a lawyer I think the other
thing though is
um when we talk about
Democrats one of the issues with
Democrats is that just like Republicans
many of them are very much married to
corporate dollars as well as
APAC okay so unless you are truly dis
disconnecting from that you can't really
remodel what the
uh function of the party is because it's
still controlled by the same levers even
if the
intentions of the um
representatives are
different am I making
sense yeah because you they're still
operating within the same system that
right that sort of um it's bigger it's
like the it's like the it's like the
good apple cops you know it's like you
come in there with a good heart but it's
bigger than
you it's bigger than you and so how do
you shift that and that requires
Grand
actions on
a cons on a um
organized
and choreographed effort and we have yet
to be able to see that with de with
Democrats because there is an
individualism among Democrats that
really is reflective of this colonial
Empire that we're in but it's that's
part of why there's still
establishment
so so unless you get a party that's
either not called
Democrats or you get Democrats who are
like there's enough of us to say we not
y'all no more we not y'all no
more which I don't think is realistic
you think them uh being you know you
said uh
sort of attached to the system and then
you also mentioned APAC right do you
think that is that contributed to their
losses explain that because people are
gonna feel a certain kind of way about
it you know what I'm
saying which people I think people if
you're they're going to think that you
are criticizing Israel that you may be
anti-semitic and all those things I'm
absolutely criticizing Israel um I am
not anti-semitic in any shape where or
form nor is criticizing Israel
anti-semitic and that is a fact so we
can continue to always amplify that
reality uh the same way that CRT is not
black history we always have to make
sure that we amplify that reality the
same way that Dei is not lowered exp no
lowered criteria so when we see the uh
bastardization of these words into
weaponization we always have to make
sure that we address it loudly and set
the record straight uh so I am critical
of the apartheid government yes
um that said you know APAC made it their
business to unseat a number of Democrats
namely Corey Bush and Jamal Bowman who
were members of the squad that you were
naming uh that you that you pointed out
you know they were members of the
progressive sect of Democrats and that
is why they were removed and many would
say that they feel AOC kind of toned
down her messaging um because she didn't
want the same fate to happen to her they
tried to get ilhan Omar out of there
didn't happen they tried to get Rashid
it didn't happen um and um you know I
think we have to acknowledge though that
if we're having conversations around
government and we're
not including the way that APAC is a
bipartisan undermining of how our votes
show up on a federal and state and you
know scale then we're not having the
real
conversation there is a real
conversation to and especially around
the strategy and uh I think do you think
Democrats need to address that in their
strategy moving forward let's hold that
thought let's listen to because I think
she's gonna talk about the dim strategy
and then we can talk about it after we
listen to a little bit more here here's
more of of Jasmine Crockett on The View
and I think that no seriously it's it's
incompetent and and I know earlier y'all
was talking about bring back the bushes
I I'm with you honey like listen I mean
you know it that was some sense of
normaly democratic norms
one thing would you support Democrats
shutting down the government as a
bargaining chip to push back against
it's not as we don't have the power to
shut the government down well to refuse
to vote for funding bills I absolutely
support that we should not be voting for
this funding bill because this funding
bill is going to gut the things that we
care about and I don't believe that we
can enter into good faith negotiations
with people that literally could care
less about their word we saw what
happened with a continuing resolution
that kept the government open until
March 14th because Elon sent out a tweet
that changed the trajectory of
negotiations that had taken place with
duly elected members of the House the
Senate as well as the president so my
concern is this guy has decided that
after monies were appropriated to
literally turn off the spet of money
just at will because he wanted to do it
who's to say that if we enter into good
faith negotiations and we get some of
the things that we feel like are good
for the American people that he won't
just do what he wants to do and ignore
the stuff he doesn't want to do so I
don't think that we should be voting for
this they have a trump Trifecta y'all
better figure it
out okay so there's a lot there but this
is really about strategy moving forward
uh you mentioned you know not being
connected
toh APAC or groups like that I was gonna
say like it's not just APAC it's it's
lobbyists it's you know so it's not just
ape right it's it's karma
well I just want to clarify so people
can hear goad go do your thing tell go
ahead they Farm a big oil you know like
Insurance like there like I don't what's
happening right now is so many Americans
are
learning the ways in which what they
thought government was it is not right
and so one of those things is the very
one plus one way that corporations
affect government in corrupt ways and
one of that one of those ways is they
don't
and then there's a quid pro quo and
whether that's said in name or n it
takes place and the largest Don
donations for these parties come from
corporations that also require things to
be moved you know in their Direction in
order for them yes NRA in order oh also
by the way let me just point out that
summer Lee is another one who defied the
efforts to um unseed her but there's you
know I saw today talking about
corruption and he was like this is a
corrupt country and I was
like he's like that's he's like and
that's terrible that's why we are
gutting Social Security so we can have a
stronger Social Security and I was
like y'all like the i' this is a level
of gaslighting and I've been gasl this
is a level of gaslighting that is I mean
it's un it's honestly remarkable but as
a nation we've been gasl for a long time
but I I derailed what were you what were
you so let's talk about because you've
been very critical of the Democrats you
didn't think that they were doing enough
you didn't you didn't like the strategy
she's saying don't help them out um with
funding I mean and that's like the
bottom line okay well go that's what I
want to know so then what would you have
Democrats do in this situation and the
situation that we're in now because you
know as you you said he is the king
right now am I wrong am I
right well that's where you know part of
my
um frustration comes is that I was
saying this before we got
here and so it's like to be here and act
like it's a new
problem just really frustrates me and
she actually said it where she was like
project 2025 was out here for a minute
and Democrats were not addressing it so
um when you ask me like what do they do
now
part of my frustration is that and I see
this a lot of the internets people being
like I don't need Democrats that tell me
every time something is constit
unconstitutional yeah I saw we ran that
yesterday demat Donald Trump will do
something and Democrats come out and go
that is UNC thank you very much yeah
thank you like that's not helpful so
what I think is helpful um one I think
that there was a really
frustrating um
optic of watching Democrats in their
coats you know very respectable being
stopped you sound like me go go
on afraid to say [ __ ] or ass or you know
and we know that they talk like that for
real they actually by the way on the
hill they do talk like that so they're
keeping up appearances for whom I don't
know and they're doing this in the face
of folks who have made it abundantly
clear they don't care about your
appearances like you're not doing that
for the people and you're not doing like
like what I think what really threw a
lot of us off was when we saw that one
skin head man standing in front uh I
forgot what the building was maybe the
treasury he was standing in front the
building and you had Maxine Waters and
Maxwell Frost and other Democrats who
were like so you're not going to let us
in he's like all right and then they
turned around and I'm like there's eight
of
y'all bum rush right go this is
something you get arrested for go
and and so some might say well what
would be the point of them going to jail
and those are people who don't
understand resistance and that has been
trained out of us the point of going to
jail there's a number of reasons one you
go to jail because now let's say they
keep you in jail the attention now comes
to them being in jail and the people
continue to build up the noise that
these people are in jail and as people
continue to build up that concerns those
who feel like they have a control of the
populace and all they care about is
feeling like they have a control of the
populace two you go to jail because you
show the people that you are willing to
lose it all for them yeah and people
need to see that when they voted for you
to go in office and actually do
something for them especially when you
haven't even really done much and people
will say well how could they well I
didn't have both the house and the
senate in the beginning but that's
another conversation for another time
the people want them to do like they
have the permission like it actually be
uh it would give them some Street people
are like can you please break the law
did you say Street credit can you break
the law because they're breaking the law
they look they want to say it say wait
say it one more time please they are
breaking the law and Tom Homan wants uh
AOC investigated for telling people
about their rights which First Amendment
right which is not against the law and I
said yesterday these are people who
would have who would have you know
arrested Harriet Tubman and prosecuted
her right so there's no
kind of difference here they arrested
Martin Luther King he was in jail so
long he wrote a book right a letter that
was long enough for a book okay so look
there was a protest fancy Coates be
annoying me I ain't gonna lie to you can
y'all put a Patagonia on or something
like because this whole ful length wool
is killing me who is this when I see
them out there in the fancy coats in the
full length walls oh my
God I be like people can you be real
right
look I want you I want you to uh watch
this because I went to a protest and
then uh I'm just going to adjust some
lighting because the sun is coming in
but go ahead watch this and then I want
I want to know what you think for sure
hey can I interview you guys interview
it's cold why are you out
here why isn't everybody out here
because the government has capitulated
the government has capitulated to a few
billionaires is what is what it's done
the country is being raped um where
we're we're we're we're giving away all
of our just you know voluntarily is
what's happening and um it's really
scary times for most of the country
would you and the world what do you want
from Congress or Senate I want the
Congress to stand up I want them to like
look at the Constitution do what they've
been elected to do be independent have
an independent voice and represent the
people not just bow down to an
individual and certainly protect people
from raping and pillaging our
information our privacy our rights there
are no more than what just we're giving
our protections not just for you and me
but for everybody else that we know
obviously your IRS with what's happening
with Donald Trump and Elon Musk but how
do you feel about the Democrats what do
you think they should be doing well I I
I mean my ey is my there's a lot there's
a lot of ey what should the Democrats be
doing being stronger bringing guns to
the right fight and not and not knives
and not and not quibbling amongst
themselves but you know what I get it
I'm a Democrat so I [ __ ] get it I
there there's a lot of constituencies so
it's really difficult however now is a
crisis and we need to really Act be very
very vocal not mince words and and and
be very very present don't mince words
don't be so polite don't be so um don't
be so holy what are you bowing down to a
lot sort of propriety are you trying to
pretend like the government is still
really like like you
know speak your [ __ ] mind and do it
loudly that's that's what I want thank
you it's nice to meet you so this is
what I I love it when people right at
the end they're like look they say
everything needed to say he's just like
speak your effing mind right it's and so
what do you make of what he said I agree
with everything he said for the for the
sole purpose of you think protests work
sorry you think people should be
protesting go on sorry there's a multi
it's a multipronged approach there has
to be a multipronged approach to all of
this some people can't go out and
protest for a myriad of reasons right uh
once upon a time I was all in the
streets all the time these days I have a
bit more anxiety in groups so don't do
it as much but I find my way in other
ways to protest um I think that there's
educating people there's like he said
bring the guns to the fight there's a
myriad of ways that we find ourselves as
a part of solution in Revolution Korea
South Korea has a great template for
that like if you cannot be out there
then how about supporting organizations
that are out there that are providing
food etc etc so we don't we're not
organized in that way yet but I do
believe we have the ability to be I do
believe we have the ability to be
however I do think one of the key
elements of us having the ability to be
is the fact that there are so many
people that are still looking to their
elected officials for guidance for
leadership for encouragement and when
they're not providing that um outside of
just the same
tonality and the same um kind of like
reservation right that is take that they
do when they're on the senate floor or
on the Congress floor I mean on the uh
house floor it just feels like another
day at work just we're outside on a on a
field trip and
um well what what Amanda what are they
afraid of I don't understand I don't
understand what they're afraid of I
think they're we're at a moment I hate I
went to din I don't think that they're
afraid as much as I think that they're
indoctrinated you don't think they're
just that they don't know what to do I
don't think they know what to do but I
think they don't know what to do because
they have been indoctrinated so many
Americans don't know what to do because
we've been indoctrinated we exist in a
silo where many of us have not even seen
what Revolution looks like many of not
many of us have not even seen what
resistance looks like mind you there's
people resisting all over the world
every day right and for much less than
this they comfortable are we too
comfortable you said that that's what
you mean by
indoctrination we're too uninformed
[Music]
it's not that we're
we're we are when I when you say we're
too comfortable I think we are
too Blissful in this ignorance that we
are comfortable and we're actually not
but because we don't see enough of
outside you know you were on cable news
they rarely show what's going on in the
world rarely especially when it has to
do with resistance because cable news
and mainstream media is here for for the
purpose of suppressing resistance
they're not trying to incite the people
they are tools of the propaganda machine
so the effort to show that and encourage
people is not going to be utilized on
those Airwaves that's why there's such a
egregious effort to silence you know
social media in that way however when
you look at France they didn't even they
didn't even change the pension they just
talked about it they talked about it
they didn't even take away pension they
was just like hey we might do this and
France was like oh hell no
we burning
cars this is and in Grenada um the same
person was in power for quite some time
and then he got a little too comfy and
tried to do the same thing with pensions
and grenadians was like whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa get him out of there
get him out of there immediately and
that was that there wasn't it wasn't
even like a confusion it was just not
finished party done so I say all of that
to say that that Americans have been
tricked into thinking they're
comfortable and and and and this is done
by small incrementation over time that
we don't argue enough about right when
they like we talk about how when they
took your rights from Ry Wade that's
when everything should have been just
handled and I'm being careful with my
language for obvious reasons but that is
when we as people needed to
demonstrate in a way that did not leave
confusion about our
frustration yeah or or even just give
them uh an opening to for that uh
confusion to go oh oh oh nothing really
happened so we're gonna we're gonna push
further maybe this is okay this is a
perfect time standby would you mentioned
because you mentioned corporate media um
this is a the a great time to tell
people to subscribe to our content um
and make sure you become a member the
membership is at the top of the chat
make sure you hit the thumbs up because
it affects the algorithm and more people
get to hear and see M Amanda seals and I
uh Amanda seals who is an artistic
artistic I want to make sure I get that
right intellectual and the host of a
YouTube show views from Amanda land and
you should look that up and you should
also click on that and go check out um
Amanda seals but make sure you hit the
the thumbs up and we're talking about
what's happening here and are we too
comfortable and Democratic strategy and
just everything stream of Consciousness
that we want to talk about did you
finish your thought on that one or did I
interrupt
no I can finish it um so this weekend
I'm doing my one woman show what would
the ancestors say in as a free show at
Lincoln
Center and in that show uh the per the
show uses comedy and uh lecture and
characters to ask the question what
would our ancestors say about where we
are and what kind of ancestors are we
going to be for those who come behind us
and I have a segment of the show where I
talk about the here [ __ ] damn
laws the aamn laws are the laws that
were
passed not because it was morally the
correct thing to do not because it was
ethically and just to do so but because
the people stood up in a way that was
undeniable and finally they were like oh
hga
damn so bloody Sunday happens in Selma
the people stood up in Selma the people
said we going to walk across this bridge
even though we know that the devil is on
the other side with hate in his eyes
with guns and batons and horses we're
going to walk across this bridge for our
to demonstrate our desire to be American
to be to exist as American citizens in
the full existence of our rights which
includes voting which we are being
denied the right to do and they did that
and the Press was there and um thus this
got broadcast all over the nation and
now liberals who had been pretending
like this was not their business were
like o now we see it we can't not see it
which we saw with George Floyd and what
happened so then right after that you
see that they pass uh I think that was
when they passed the voting rights law
but that was in response it wasn't ahead
of time it was response and it was in
response people put their bodies on the
line as somebody who has been out
protesting right I have put my body on
the line as somebody who understands
what it means to lose it all
I put my whole career on the line to
Simply say hey this genocide is
unacceptable so I know that a lot of us
are like well I'm not ready to do that
which is why at the top of my website
Amanda seals.com it says you know ask
yourself what is your courage what level
of Courage are you at because Americans
have been taught that we're big and bad
we're not we're not big and bad and
um we have seen vers of Americans who
are big and bad and black lives matter
was an incredibly powerful movement that
ended up getting squelched um by open by
reopening the
country and by giving by by giving
juneth making juneth a Federal holiday
which no one asked for as a response to
Black lives matter I mean the the Quest
for it to become a Federal holiday
should not have been attached to that um
and for the record a num out of all the
states that like or all the cities that
put like black lives matter paintings on
their sidewalks I think only five of
them actually removed qualified
immunity so look BLM as you said you
mentioned BLM has become a preor of Dei
has become a pejorative like CRT and
like woke right they've you know um
changed the meaning of what it actually
wait I have a thought can I say this
thought real quick yes how's going to
say hell yeah go
ahead you know one of the other issues
that I think is really in our way is cuz
like I look at the chat
right the disdain we have for each
other is
so
pervasive and it is so unhelpful to
anybody it is so freewheeling now it is
so
um triggered and weaponized and instead
of
us asking questions from genuine curious
places we're doing
indictments instead of us um sharing
information oftentimes it's done in a
let me tell you what I know about more
than you and we don't exist as a
community with with love we don't and
we I know that because when I left LA
and I moved and I moved to a new state
and I moved to a new community I ex I
understood what it meant to exist with
love because I moved here and within two
weeks I had four different Neighbors
show up to say hey welcome to the
neighborhood I lived in my neighborhood
in La for three years and what I got was
a woman down the street sell um
posting um posting propaganda saying
that I am anti-jewish which I am not in
any shape way or form so I just
challenge all of us you know sometimes
we're like damn what can we do it just
seems impossible we have to start on a
very very basic level at even acting
like we care what happens to another
person and if we're going to be in these
chats and we're GNA be on these
Instagram and social media Pages talking
to each other with such disdain we are
representing the same oppressor that we
claim to be against we don't actually
care about each other yeah I have you
know you reminded me of that I so you
know I'm not on X anymore I'm not I
don't go into a lot of these places
because I'm just simply I'm just simply
tired of people trying to make me feel
bad about myself I don't need that
brother
brother and I don't I think people think
that's normal now it's become so
normalized has become normal it has
become and it's become normal to buy
into the rhetoric again this is a
transition but it's become normal for
people to you know um to to co-opt the
meaning of language and words like BLM
which was meant which came from a good
place like diversity Equity inclusion
which come from which came from a good
place or any of those things um yeah
and I think the Republicans are great at
messaging so much so that people fall
for it right obviously the people who
support them fall for it sometimes I
believe that we it's not just
Republicans right Democrats are as well
yeah well I'm not a Democrat but you
know I I don't believe in parties
because you know I think they all I did
not know that no I'm an independent I'm
not I'm not a Democrat um and it's not
that I but that's a whole other level to
say I don't believe in parties I'm wi
brother I don't believe in in political
parties because I think like there's
look I think that I have some
conservative leanings I do and I have
some liberal leanings but I like action
and I think all too many times our
politicians don't deliver for us and um
we need to figure out maybe we should
come up with a party call you know using
corporate language the deliverables
right we want to know what the
deliverables are that's the that's the
party the D party that I'm with So
speaking
of let's talk about go you know it's
it's Two Hosts right so it's like this
ain't your show shut up yeah no no no
that's all
right that has never bothered me and
I've noticed you know when I notice that
that sometimes there's a competition
like if I go on to every once in a while
like another person talk show or like a
late night show and I'm like this
person's competing with me really and
yeah and I'm always like it's their show
but when folks were on my show I always
wanted my guests to shine because I know
I'm gonna be here tomorrow I'm gonna be
sitting in this five minutes from now
but they won't so while they're on let
them shine why am I competing with you
so I've just been letting you
talk I have you on because I want to
hear from you you know what I'm saying I
do because I'm the same way
when I do smart funny in black and I
have my two guests competing against
each other I'll back up and just sit on
the side of the stage and watch them do
what they're doing if I feel like I need
to interject or move interject and move
the show along I'll do it like I'm
trying to now so look so let's talk
about this diversity equity and
inclusion this is very you know the
airplanes have been falling out of the
sky there's been an airplane Collision
uh that just happened now or an airplane
crash let me get the um the specifics on
what another one so uh it says a midair
Collision involving two small planes in
Southern Arizona killed at least two
people uh on Wednesday morning
authorities says fellow air safety
investigators said that two people were
on board each plane as they collided
near Morana Regional Airport on the
outskirts of tcon and so now I mean look
there's a there's an interesting graphic
that we'll put up and I want to talk to
you about it but here's the thing um oh
where is it so you know everyone is so
stuck on Dei right now and they're so
stuck on pronouns right now so there's
this graphic that explains let's show
what an airplane is we'll put it up
right an airplane actually is that's the
lift that's the weight that's the thrust
in front and then the drag in the back
and then someone put this up because
this is how the Republicans will explain
it pronouns weight drag
D that's how they see internet an air
operates so what do you think that isn't
how they really see an in it that's how
do they how how do Republicans or how do
how does magga and the Trump folks who
are in charge were blaming everything on
Dei how do they see what's happening how
can they blame this on diversity equity
and inclusion or on the previous
Transportation secretary or on the
previous president when none of this
happened when they were when they were
it goes back to what I said because they
know that we don't care about each
other so they know that all they have to
do is continue to pke that little you
know that little pressure point um that
will make enough
people swell up and you know talk about
this thing for them because all they're
really trying to do is consolidate power
yeah they know they know that people do
not um don't know how to love each other
through their differences and so through
that they are wielding the hatred to
continuously give them power that by the
way they don't use to even empower the
people that they're
using um this any any application of Dei
or any of anything outside of mechanics
to to address these planes really should
be your like Thing They Don't Care About
Us right like that's what your bell
should ring
they don't they're not talking about the
people on the planes they're the and
someone said who's they we're talking
about you know the person who is the
head of um transportation now who took
PE budha jud's place right we're talking
about these government
officials right Shan Duffy we're talking
about um these government officials like
Donald Trump who are basically like oh
yeah it's terrible but you know that's
what you get when you put a black in
black in the cockpit you know I mean
like that's the type of conversations
that are being had and again I want to
just bring to people people something
very simple that they can grab on to
because I think a lot of these
conversations around politics around the
uh infrastructure of things they do go
over our heads by Design right like
there's an
entire business around taxes it should
not require an
entire
industry to give away your money right
you shouldn't have to pay somebody to
pay
somebody but they create these systems
to make it difficult so try simplify are
you like Donald Trump do you think we
should get rid of the
IRS I'm not saying I don't know I think
that at the end of the day we are not
taxing fairly if the IRS was existing
for the enactment of fair taxation then
so be it so I I am not like Donald Trump
in any way don't ever say that
again yes yes
man um but the I I was saying all that
because always want to ground it in
something very very basic which is
really just asking yourself like do I
care about every do I care about anybody
else yeah like and and some of us might
say I don't
care enough I don't care enough and just
for the record again Dei was never about
lowering criteria right it was about
expanding who has access to the position
based on ways in which they were limited
before MH the criteria remain the same
it was not a top down shift it was a
lateral shift if we're only looking at
these people who meet the criteria what
happens if we expand and look at all of
these people who meet the criteria wow
we're getting such a bigger group of
folks to look at and that's important
yeah we need to fish in the ocean rather
than a pond so um look this is fun I
think that I think that one more thing
that I want to tell you remember that
people lie and people fell for this lie
but um yeah and this and this talks
about who we are and our lack of
knowledge or information because this
was Donald Trump back during the
election and this is him now and people
have fallen for this lie watch the day I
take the oath of office I will rapidly
Drive prices down and we will make
America affordable again we're going to
make it affordable again and and
inflation is back I'm only here for 2
and A2 weeks that was J inflation back
no think of it inflation's back and they
said oh Trump infl I had nothing to do
with yeah and he said I wanted to throw
my phone yes he said didn't he say
within minutes or hours after taking the
Oval Office and here it's been a month
and then uh he also told people that he
could not lower the price of eggs and
all of the things that they hit Joe
Biden for regardless of how you felt
about Joe Biden yeah but it's true it's
different for him somehow the rules have
changed why does it change for this
white man instead of the other
one well baby that's what that's how it
always
is okay that's how it always is and I
think that's what I say when I say like
we are where we are because an
environment was created for this to get
this bad yeah Joe Biden was also a
liar you know Joe Biden was also
somebody who had done and created great
harm to to to swads of American
communities right um but it was fine for
certain people because he was a Democrat
so the same way that we're like oh my
God I can't believe he's lying there
were people that were like oh my God I
can't believe he's lying so this
continues and now it's just it every
time it gets more and more extreme you
know why because every time they get
away with it and they push it a little
more push it a little more the last
administration had got away with
genocide and and sticking troops
political because they were police but
they were acting like troops sticking
troops on college students that were
peacefully protesting another country
they got away with that nobody on a on a
legislative level with any level of
power said hey we should not do this in
fact they said no okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay so they continue to
push and push and they're building cop
cities all over this nation with the
anticipation we're going to push a bit
more and at some point we gonna push too
far and these people gonna turn up and
we're going to be ready for them they've
already occupied your cities
so
we have to decide enough is enough and
we have to decide what does it look like
when enough is enough you know February
28th is supposed to to be a national day
of no spending national day of everybody
saying no spending we're not putting our
money out there it's a wrap done and
that is one way that I know a lot of
people feel like they can stick it to
the government I will tell you all this
is not going to get fixed quickly and
it's not going to get fixed easily
because we have to train we have to
train in what it means to be Community
we have to train in what it means to not
think as individuals we have to train
and how to know when it's time to be the
lieutenant and not the leader you know
we need to train As Americans we are out
of we don't we're out of practice we
were a nation that did that but we don't
we ain't been about that so we need to
train and so there's going to be a bit
of practice on this front and some
people right now who may be looking at
me saying oh my God I can't stand her in
a few months I hope they're like man I'm
out here though now I'm out here I get
it and so I don't want anyone I don't
want us to get discouraged but I do not
but do need us to get determined and um
I I I know that we want the Democrats to
do what they need to do they probably
aren't because they're not trained
either and at the end of the day Jasmine
is a black woman from Dallas so she just
cut different in
general and let me just last thing the
last thing I want to say dime yep when
you had said like the Republicans say
things that create division
so do Democrats this is the work of
government particularly on a federal
level that's why these parties is so
dangerous because they're gangs and when
they were saying like oh if you are
saying that you don't want to vote for
so and so because you don't stand for
genocide then you're a problem you're
literally
sicking your constituency on their
fellow
people instead of saying let's actually
find out what the issue is that's what
we should be doing Coalition building
and so the division the division which
y'all think is oh I'm standing on
something is you're being used you're
being used I saw people in here saying
that I was spewing divisive rhetoric
about
gasa no what I was always saying was if
there's going to be any shot at winning
this it's going to require everybody
else but the people who are over there
and in order to get everybody else on
board you have to care about all the
things that they're talking about that
are legitimate you're going to have to
care about the people who feel like
working class is being forgotten you're
going to have to care about the people
who are in the lgbtq plus Community who
feel like they're not getting any policy
you're going to have to care about the
uh members of the Arab community and the
Muslim Community who feel like they are
literally watching their entire peoples
be obliterated you're going to have to
care about those people even in the most
modom of ways because it doesn't really
take much but even in the most mod of
ways you're going to have to demonstrate
that and if you're not willing to do
that then you're not willing to actually
Garner their support I say all that to
say I think this whole thing was rigged
anyway Amanda seals that's the topic for
another time I said an hour you've been
here for an hour and 21 minutes we've
been doing this thank you Amanda I
really appreciate it uh Amanda seals
artistic intellectual and host of the
YouTube show views from Amanda land yay
than Amanda Monday through Wednesday at
Amanda sales on YouTube thank you Amanda
thank you Don thanks for having me good
to have you thank you so much so um
hello everyone thank you look I'm so
glad that you are here with us today
this was our a very special um stream
that we're doing live stream that we're
doing today because we happen to get
Amanda seals and we wanted to do it
we're going to be live for you at five
o'clock not to worry and I hope you at
least um that you learned from that that
you enjoyed it and that you you learn
and from the conversation um this is how
I believe people should talk and I you
know I liked hearing what she had to say
so make sure you hit the thumbs up make
sure you like And subscribe we
appreciate your support I want to thank
all the people who joined the
memberships um Donan you're not alone
others make us feel bad for speaking the
truth when we are of color we are
challenged and hated more I say do not
stop speaking the truth thank you for
inviting Amanda Seal's much love thank
you good vibes for that and thank you
everyone for your support we appreciate
you here more than ever so make sure you
can come back at 5 o'clock we're going
to have a conversation I have much minut
many many many many things to talk about
okay so I will see you in just a little
bit at 5:00 pm Eastern for live at 5
turn the TV off thanks everyone for
watching your support means the world to
us so make sure you hit the like button
and you subscribe to our channel to make
sure that you never ever miss a video
we're live every day 10: a.m. eastern
time we drop even more content at 2:
p.m. Eastern and 5:00 p.m. Eastern and
if you want more Don Lemon show content
we'd love for you to become a member of
the lmon community where you will
receive access to special Community
posts you'll get exclusive content and
members only live shows so head over to
our Channel page or click the join
button on this video again thank you for
watching